radianttranslations.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy Policy - Radiant Translations

Users on radianttranslations.com agree to the Privacy Policy listed below.

**Privacy Policy**

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Personal Information**

We collect your information when you: sign in or make an account, sign up to receive email notifications, and comment. This information includes but is not necessarily limited to your username, email address and IP address, however you may access the site anonymously.

We also collect information that is not personally identifiable, this can include what browser you use, that platform that you used to access our site, and what search terms you used to get here.

**Cookies**

The site may use “cookies” in order to enhance user experience. Users’ internet browsers place cookies on their hard drives for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may change the settings of their browser in order to deny cookies, however some features of the site may not function correctly.

**How we use collected information**

Radiant Translations may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * To improve customer service 
    * Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

  * To personalize user experience 
    * We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

  * To improve our Site 
    * We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

  * To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature 
    * To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Third party websites**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at radianttranslations@gmail.com.

This document was last updated on October 7th, 2016
